Finding Aid for the A&M Records Records PASC-M.0269
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sound recordings, 1910-1999; Series 12.
  - Commercial popular music: 33 1/3 rpm LP sound recordings, Subseries 6.
    - Barry Manilow Live, 1977 (Box 177, Folder 26)
      Riders to the Stars -- Why Don't We Live Together -- Looks Like We Made It -- New York City Rhythm -- A Very Strange Medley -- Jump Shout Boogie Medley -- This One's For You -- Beautiful Music (Part I) -- Daybreak -- Lay Me Down -- Weekend In New England -- Studio Musician -- Beautiful Music (Part II) -- Could It Be Magic/Mandy -- It's A Miracle -- It's Just Another New Year's Eve -- I Write the Songs -- Beautiful Music (Part III).
    - Silverado, Original motion picture soundtrack, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 177, Folder 28)
      Silverado Main Title -- The Getaway/Riding As One -- Ezra's Death -- The McKendrick Attack -- Augie Is Taken -- On To Silverado -- Augie's Rescue -- Goodbye, Cobb -- End Credits ("We'll Be Back").
    - Pressure Sensitive, 1975; 1 12" sound disc (Box 177, Folder 29)
      Always There -- Momma -- Never Be the Same -- Tell Me Something Good -- Nothing To Lose -- Tidal Wave -- Why Do You Laugh At Me -- Mis' Mary's Place.
    - A New World Record, 1976; 1 12" sound disc (Box 177, Folder 30)
      Tightrope -- Telephone Line -- Rockaria! -- Mission (A World Record) -- So Fine -- Livin' Thing -- Above the Clouds -- Do Ya -- Shangri-La.
    - Boogie Woogie Rhythm and Blues, 1986; 1 12" sound disc (Box 177, Folder 32)
      Publisher no.: IR 9188
      Big Bash Boogie -- The Grinder -- Beanface Boogie -- So Low Blues -- The Island Groove -- Rock 'n Boogie -- Balboa Boogie -- Boogie D. Lux -- Waltzing Blues.
    - Friends and Strangers, 1977; 1 12" sound disc (Box 177, Folder 33)
      Goodtime Ride -- Saturday Evening -- Friends and Strangers -- Nuthin' 'Bout Nothin' -- New Day -- Life In Paradise -- Same Old Story -- Just Love.
    - City To City, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 177, Folder 34)
      Publisher no.: UA-LA840-G
      The Ark -- Baker Street -- Right Down the City Line -- City To City -- Stealin' Time -- Mattie's Rag -- Whatever's Written In Your Heart -- Home and Dry -- Island -- Waiting For the Day.
    - Lenny Bruce, Carnegie Hall, February 4, 1961, The Complete Unabridged Concert, 1972; 3 12" sound discs (Box 177, Folder 35)
      Introduction / Don Friedman -- Miracle on 57th Street -- The Airlines -- Sound -- The Kidnap -- Point of View -- Ku Klux Klan -- Homosexuality -- Girl Singing -- The Flag and Communism -- Dear Abby -- Equality -- Internal Review -- Pills -- Burlesque House -- Judge Saperstein Decision -- A What's It Mean -- Kennedy Acceptance Speech -- On Humor -- Nightclubs -- Dykes and Faggots -- Las Vegas Tits and Ass -- The Clap -- Christ and Moses -- On Contemporaries -- Shelley Berman -- The Operation -- The Joke -- The End.
    - A Very Special Christmas, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Santa Clause is Coming to Town (The Pointer Sisters) -- Winter Wonderland (Eurythmics) -- Do You Hear What I Hear (Whitney Houston) -- Merry Christmas Baby (Bruce Springsteen and the E Street Band) -- Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas (The Pretenders) -- I Saw Mommy Kissing Santa Claus (John Cougar Mellencamp) -- Gabriel's Message (Sting) -- Christmas in Hollis (Run D.M.C.) -- Christmas (Baby Please Come Home) (U2) -- Santa Baby (Madonna) -- The Little Drummer Boy (Bob Seger and the Silver Bullet Band) -- Run Rudolph Run (Bryan Adams) -- Back Door Santa (Bon Jovi) -- The Coventry Carol (Alison Moyet) -- Silent Night (Stevie Nicks).
    - Flashback Live, 1987; 7" disc. (Box 53, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: AM-39101
    - Strength In Numbers, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: SP 5115
      Somebody Like You -- Like No Other Night -- Last Night -- Once In A Lifetime -- Just A Little Love -- Has There Ever Been A Goodbye -- One In A Million -- Heart's On Fire -- Against the Night -- Never Give An Inch.
    - Hold On Loosely and Rockin' Into the Night, 1984 (Box 171, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: SP 17309
      Hold On Loosely -- Rockin' Into the Night.
    - Cuts Like a Knife, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: SP-6-4919
    - Retail Sampler, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: SP 17321
      Lonely Nights -- Somebody -- Summer of '69 -- This Time -- Straight From the Heart -- Run To You -- Take Me Back -- Heaven -- Cuts Like A Knife -- Fits Ya Good.
    - Reckless, 1984; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 5013
      One Night Love Affair -- She's Only Happy When She's Dancin' -- Run to You -- Heaven -- Somebody -- Summer of '69 -- Kids Wanna Rock -- It's Only Love -- Long Gone -- Ain't Gonna Cry.
    - I Love The Way You Make Me Feel, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: 28965 1200 1
    - The Age of Aquarius, 1 12" sound disc (Box 177, Folder 31)
      Publisher no.: SCS-92005
      Medley: Aquarius/Let the Sunshine In (The Flesh Failures) -- Let It Be Me -- Sunshine Of Your Love -- Blowing Away -- Workin' On A Groovy Thing -- Wedding Bell Blues -- He's A Runner -- The Winds Of Heaven -- Those Were the Days -- The Hideaway -- Don'tcha Hear Me Callin' To Ya -- Skinny Man.
    - The Best, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: SP-3207
    - Bi-Coastal, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: SP-4825
    - Jump Street (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: 75021 2359 1
    - North On South Street (Box 32, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: 75021 5345 1
      4 copies
    - Beyond, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: C28Y3046
    - A&M Gold Series (Box 33, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: C28Y3054
    - Rise, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: C25Y3045
      3 copies
    - Wild Romance, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: C28Y3048
    - Red Hot, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: PROSI 17
    - Rise, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: SP 3274
    - Beyond, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: SP 3717
    - Magic Man, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: SP 3728
    - Fandango, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: SP 3731
      6 copies
    - Herb Alpert Presents Pete Jolly (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: SP 4145
    - Just You And Me, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: SP 4591
    - Main Event: Herb Alpert & Hugh Masekela Live (Box 36, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: SP-4727
      Also performed by: Hugh Masekela.
    - Blow Your Own Horn, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: SP-4949
    - Wild Romance, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: SP-5082
    - Wild Romance, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Keep Your Eye On Me, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: SP-5125
      5 copies
    - Under a Spanish Moon, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: SP-5209
    - My Abstract Heart, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: SP 5273
    - Herb Alpert and Hugh Masekela, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: SP 728
      Also performed by Hugh Masekela. 3 copies
    - Rise, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: SP 12022
    - Rotations, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: SP 12032
      Promotional copy. Two copies.
    - Other Side, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: SP 12145
    - Keep Your Eye On Me, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: SP 12226
    - Making Love In The Rain, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: SP 12247
    - Red Hot, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: SP 12078
    - Magic Man, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: SP 17163
      12" single.
    - Noche de Amor, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: SP 37006
      3 copies.
    - Guard Session (Box 44, Folder 32)
      Publisher no.: GXSCV-10817
    - [Selections], 1989 July 7; 1 12" sound disc (Box 62, Folder 1)
      Legs -- When the Lights Go Wown Low -- Just a Dream Away -- Kalimba -- Soho.
      Side 2. Mastercut.
    - The Robert W. Morgan Special Of The Week, 1980 October 4 - 5 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: SWS-804-1
    - Christmas Album, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: C28Y3092
    - S.R.O (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: C25Y3108
    - Greatest Hits (Box 34, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: SP-3267
      three copies
    - What Now My Love (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: SP 3265
      four copies
    - Volume 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: SP 3262
      five copies
    - Going Places (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: SP 4112
    - What Now My Love (Box 34, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: SP 4114
    - The Christmas Album, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: SP-3113
    - Solid Brass (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: SP 3268
    - Greatest Hits, vol.2, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: SP 3269
    - You smile- The Song Begins, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: SP 3620
    - Warm (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: SP 4190
    - Herb Alpert's Ninth (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: SP 4134
    - Summertime (Box 36, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: SP 4314
    - Coney Island, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: AP 4521
    - Bullish, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: SP-5022
    - Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass Foursider, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: 0598
    - Die 20 grssten Erfolge, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: TV1
    - 40 Greatest, 1977; 2 12" sound discs (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: NE 1005
      Lonely Bull -- Green Peppers -- Never On Sunday -- Spanish Flea -- If I Were A Rich Man -- Love Potion No. 9 -- Walk Don't Run -- Carmen -- Moments -- Brasila -- Taste Of Honey -- Hello Dolly -- Jerusalem -- Sunny -- Mexican Corn -- Work Song -- Warm -- Third Man Theme -- Girl From Ipanema -- Mexican Shuffle -- Tijuana Taxi -- Mame -- Acapulco 1922 -- Cabaret -- Marching Thru Madrid -- What Now My Love -- I Can't Go On Living -- She Touched Me -- Panama -- Zorba The Greek -- A Banda -- Memories Of Madrid -- Walk In The Black Forest -- Shadow Of Your Smile -- Casino Royale -- Moon River -- El Presidente -- More -- Wade In The Water -- This Guy's In Love.
    - Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass Christmas Album, 1968; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: SP 3113
      Winter Wonderland -- Jingle Bells -- My Favorite Things -- The Christmas Song -- Las Mannitas -- Sleigh Ride -- The Bell That Couldn't Jingle -- Let It Snow, Let It Snow, Let It Snow -- Jingle Bell Rock -- Jesu, Joy of Man's Desiring.
      Voices and strings arranged by Shorty Rogers.
    - 8 Ball, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      45 rpm.
    - Going Places, 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 3264
      Tijuana Taxi -- I'm Getting Sentimental Over You -- More and More Amor -- Spanish Flea -- Mae -- 3rd Man Theme -- Walk Don't Run -- Felicia -- And the Angels Sing -- Cinco de Mayo -- A Walk in the Black Forest -- Zorba the Greek.
    - Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass Greatest Hits, 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 3267
      Lonely Bull -- Spanish Flea -- Getting Sentimental Over You -- Love Potion No. 9 -- Never on Sunday -- Mexican Shuffle -- Taste of Honey -- Tijuana Taxi -- South of the Border -- America -- Whipped Cream -- Zorba the Greek.
    - Keep Your Eye on Me, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 5125
      Keep Your Eye on Me -- Hot Shot -- Diamonds -- Traffic Jam -- Cat Man Do -- Pillow -- Our Song -- Making Love in the Rain -- Rocket to the Moon -- Stranger on the Shore.
    - Main Event, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 4727
      Foreign Natives -- People Make the World Go Round -- Besame Mucho -- I'm Comin' Home -- She Been -- Kalahari Nights -- Shame the Devil -- Mama Way.
      Also performed by Hugh Masekela and Mosa Jonas Gwangwa.
    - Rise, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Disc is clear.
    - The Beat of the Brass, 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 4146
      Cabaret -- Thanks for the Memory -- Monday, Monday -- Slick -- Panama -- A Beautiful Friend -- She Touched Me -- Talk to the Animals -- Belz Mein Shtetele Belz = My Home Town -- This Guy's in Love With You -- The Robin.
    - The Brass Are Comin', 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 4228
      The Brass are Comin' (The Little Train of Caipira) -- Sunny -- Moon River -- You Are My Life -- I'm An Old Cowhand -- Good Moring, Mr. Sunshine -- I'll Be Back -- Robbers and Cops -- Country Lake -- The Maltese Melody -- Moments -- Anna.
    - The Lonely bull, 1962; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 3101
      The Lonely Bull -- El Lobo -- Tijuana Sauerkraut -- Desafinado -- Mexico -- Never on Sunday -- Struttin' With Maria -- Let it Be Me -- Acapulco -- Limbo Rock -- Crawfish -- A Quiet Tear.
      Also performed by the Tijuana Brass.
    - Whipped Cream & Other Delights, 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: C25Y3107
    - Whipped Cream & Other Delights (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - A Treasure Of The Aaward-Ainning Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass (Box 44, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: LWS 500 - 504
      Also performed by the Baja Marimba Band. Box set.
    - Just Like a Man! (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: 31458 8008 1
    - Waking Hours (Box 32, Folder 29)
      Publisher no.: AMA 9006
    - City Called Heaven (Box 47, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: 8958
    - Orchestral Manoeuvres In The Dark, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: ARE 37721
    - Track Record, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: SP-4987
    - Sleight Of Hand, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: SP 5130
    - Sleight Of Hand, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 15)
      Kind Words (And A Real Good Heart) -- Killing Time -- Reach Out -- Angel Man -- Laurel And the Rose -- One More Chance -- Russian Roulette -- Jesse -- Figure Of Speech -- Don Juan.
    - A Rock and Roll Alternative, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: PD-1-6080
      Sky High -- Hitch-Hikers' Hero -- Don't Miss the Message -- Georgia Rhythm -- So In To You -- Outside Woman Blues -- Everybody Gotta Go -- Neon Nites.
    - A Rock and Roll Alternative, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Talking To Oneself (Box 44, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: C60 27879 004
    - Woman (Box 35, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: SP-3709
      Also performed by the Houston Symphony.
    - Cantatas, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: ARL1-3715
      Mein Herze schwimmt im Blut, BWV 199 -- Jauchzet Gott in allen Landen, BWV 51
      Soloists: Edita Gruberova, Roman Summereder, Dsutsche Bachsolisten.
    - Six Trio Sonatas For Flute And Harpsichord, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: ARL1-3580
    - Get On Your Back!, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: SP 12508
    - Strada Facendo, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: 84764
    - Julius Wechter and the Baja Marimba Band Greatest Hits, 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Comin' in the Back Door -- Yours -- Along Comes Mary -- Spanish Eyes -- Fowl Play -- The Look of Love -- Gregory Girl -- Ghost Riders in the Sky -- Acapulco 1922 -- Some Where My Love -- Maria Elena -- Brasilia.
    - Chet Baker & Strings, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: JCL 549
    - Album de Peterhof (Box 44, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: C10 28021 006
    - Chet Baker Sings, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 34)
      Publisher no.: PJLP-11
    - Euphoria, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: SP-3188
    - Ruby, Ruby, 1977; 1 12" sound disc (Box 183)
      Publisher no.: SP 4655
      Ruby -- Nostalgia -- Latin Reaction -- Ngiculela-es una Historia = I am Singing -- Sunride -- Adios -- Blue Angel -- Midnight Tango.
    - One Night of Freedom (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: 31458 0239 1
    - Concerto No.5 in E-Flat, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 46, Folder 29)
      Publisher no.: ARM1-3690
      A recording in "The Horowitz Collection." Conducted by Fritz Reiner.
    - The Legendary A&M Sessions, 1984 (Box 171, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: SP 12510
      Diddy Wah Diddy -- Who Do You Think You're Fooling -- Moonchild -- Frying Pan -- Here I Am, I Always Am.
    - The George Benson Collection (Box 48, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: 2HW3577
    - The One For Me, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: NSPLX 41052
    - High Energy, 1979; 1 12" sound disc (Box 41, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: BR 56001
      High Energy -- I Got Your Number -- Tune It Up -- Disco Roller -- Listen To My Heart -- Save Your Energy.
    - I wanna Be Your Lover, 1980; 1 12" sound disc (Box 41, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: BR 56018
      I WQanna Be Your Lover -- Ohnie Don't Go Away -- Action -- A Moment Of Sunshine -- Night Flight -- You're So Fine -- One Thing's For Sure -- Cyclone Rock -- Don't Cry Now.
    - Bandido, 1978; 1 12" sound disc (Box 41, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: LPX 30
      Deserts Of Mars -- Welcome Home -- Moonlight Palais -- Baby Make Love -- Bandido -- Black And White -- Never Gonna Let You Go -- Will She Or Won't She.
    - Sextet (Box 48, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: 831 697-1
    - A Walk Across The Rooftops, 1983; 1 12" sound disc (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: LKH1
      A Walk Across The Rooftops -- Tinseltown In The Rain -- From Rags To Riches -- Stay -- Easter Parade -- Heatwave -- Automobile Noise.
      Also performed by Calum Malcolm and Nigel Thomas.
    - Play Song, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 43, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: JHR0002
      Olvera Street -- Play Song -- The Dancing Bishop -- No Hurry -- La Rue -- Surprise Samba.
    - Something About You, 1981; 1 12" sound disc (Box 41, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: AL 9576
      Something About You -- Break It To Me Gently -- On And On -- Tropical Love -- You Should Know By Now -- Only Love -- Holdin' Out For Love -- Stop Look Listen -- I Do Love You -- Time To Say Goodbye.
    - The Domino Theory, 85742 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - The Hunger, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      Publisher no.: FC40473
    - Victor Borge Live At The London Palladium, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: NSPL 18394
    - Ai, Ai, Ai de Mim (Box 42, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: 138292
    - Boston, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: 34188
      More Than A Feeling -- Peace of Mind -- Foreplay/Long Time -- Rock & Roll Band -- Smokin' -- Hitch A Ride -- Something About You -- Let Me Take You Home Tonight.
    - Reel Life (Box 46, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: 8414-1-R
      Bring Down the Moon -- Waiting For A Star To Fall -- Storymy Love -- Is Anybody Out There In Love -- Stay Forever -- If You Run -- One Sweet Dream -- No Apologies -- Restless Dreamer -- Someone's Got To Send Out Love.
    - Boy Meets Girl, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 29)
      Publisher no.: SP 6-5046
      Oh Girl -- Don't Tell Me We Have Nothing -- The Touch -- Kissing, Falling, Flying -- From Now On -- Be My Baby -- In Your Eyes -- I Wish You Were Here -- Pieces -- Premonitions.
    - Seven Standards 1985, vol. 1 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: MA-0203
    - Peer Pressure, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 31)
      Publisher no.: 1029
    - Stop!, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      Publisher no.: AMA 5195
    - Study In Brown (Box 42, Folder 36)
      Publisher no.: 6336 708
      Also performed by: Max Roach.
    - Love Snd Kisses From Brotherhood Of Man, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: NSPL 18490
    - Heroes And Zeros, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: SP 5166
    - Talking In Code, 1986 (Box 171, Folder 33)
    - Sing Along With Max (Box 45, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: NSPL 18361
    - Chirstmasing, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: WR 8347
      4 copies.
    - Mona With The Children, 1985; 1 12" sound disc (Box 43, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: GM 5100
      Mona With The Children -- One Moment Of Love -- People In The Rain -- Science Of Love -- Don't Tell Me -- Room Is Empty -- Panik -- Fool For Love -- Get Up.
    - Anthology (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: AMP-98001~4
    - Christmas Portrait, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: SP-3210
    - Time, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: SP 5117
    - Time, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Yesterday Once More, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: SP 6601
      Yesterday Once More -- Superstar -- Rainy Days and Mondays -- (Want You) Back In My Life Again -- Ticket To Ride -- Goodbye To Love -- Bless the Beasts and Children -- It's Going To Take Some Time -- Calling Occupants Of Interplanetary Craft -- Sweet, Sweet, Smile -- I Won't Last A Day Without You -- For All We Know -- Touch Me When We're Dancing -- There's A Kind Of Hush -- This Masquerade -- Hurting Each Other -- Please Mr. Postman -- I Need To Be In Love -- Make Believe It's Your First Time -- All You Get From Love Is A Love Song -- Top Of the World -- Becasue We Are In Love (The Wedding Song) -- We've Only Just Begun -- Those Good Old Dreams -- Sing -- Only Yesterday -- (They Long To Be) Close To You.
    - A Kind of Hush, 1976; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: SP 3197
      There's A Kind of Hush -- You -- Sandy -- Goofus -- Can't Smile Without You -- I Need To Be In Love -- One More Time -- Boat TO Sail -- I Have You -- Breaking Up Is Hard To Do.
    - Carpenters, 1971; 1 12" sound disc (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: SP 3502
      Rainy Days and Mondays / Paul Williams and Roger Nichols -- Saturday / Richard Carpenter and John Bettis -- Let Me Be the One / Paul Williams and Roger Nichols -- (A Place To) Hideaway / Randy Sparks -- For All We Know / Fred Karlin, Robb Wilson, and Arthur James -- Superstar / Leon Russell and Bonnie Bramlett -- Druscilla Penny / Richard Carpenter and John Bettis -- One Love / Richard Carpenter and John Bettis -- Bacharach/David Medley: Knowing When To Leave; Make It Easy On Yourself; (There's) Always Something There To Remind Me; I'll Never Fall In Love Again; Walk On By; Do You Know the Way To San Jose -- Sometimes / Felice (lyrics) and Henry Mancini.
    - Yesterday Once More, 1985; 2 12" sound discs (Box 183)
      Yesterday Once More -- Superstar -- Rainy Days and Mondays -- (Want You) Back in My Life Again -- Ticket to Ride -- Goodbye to Love -- Bless the Beasts and Children -- It's Going to Take Some Time -- Calling Occupants of Interplanetary Craft -- Sweet, Sweet Smile -- I Won't Last a Day Without You -- For All We Know -- Touch me When We're Dancing -- There's a Kind of Hush -- This Masquerade -- Hurting Each Other -- Please Mr. Postman -- I Need to be In Love -- Make Believe it's Your First Time -- All You Get From Love is a Love Song -- Top of the World -- Because We Are in Love (the Wedding Song) -- We've Only Just Begun -- Those Good Old Dreams -- Sing -- Only Yesterday -- (They Long to Be) Close to You.
    - Oscar!, 1987; 1 12" sound disc (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: LM 0010
      Rancho Do Carioca -- Rio Dawning -- Song For Joyce -- Summer Winds -- Air On A 6 String -- Bahia Calling -- Forgotten Dreams -- Luizana -- Cat Song -- Street Corner Samba.
    - Voz e Suor, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 40)
      Publisher no.: 31C 064 422 932
      Also performed by: Cesar Camargo Mariano.
    - Friendship, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: FC 39415
    - Tracy Chapman, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 35)
      Publisher no.: 60774-1
    - Is This Possible? (Box 44, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: C60 25691 009
    - What Price Paradise, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: SP-5148
      (p)1986 Virgin Records Ltd.
    - Two Plus Two, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 30)
      Publisher no.: 7086
      Also performed by Salsa Picante.
    - Rock Roll & Remember, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Gate Of Dreams (Box 48, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: BS3006